<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TPN</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="menu">Hello! \nThis is the main menu of our application from here you can use buttons to:
    \nSelect photo from gallery for image recognition
    \nTake a new photo using phone camera for image recognition
    \nSwitch between different ML models to select one to use
    \nLoad new models from phone storage to use</string>
    <string name="camera">Here You can take a photo and the application will run it through currently use
        Machine Learning model and then display five classes which the model will predict as the most probable</string>
    <string name="load">Here You can load new models to use. If You wan to load model that is complainant with
        our default settings (224x224 input size model recognizing labels from a dataset of 285
        plant species from Tatra National Park) just click Load Model and select appropriate .tflite file.
        However if You want to load model that differs from our default (has different size of input, recognizes cars, animals etc.)
        You need to provide a manifest file (a simple json) that describes the the models input and output.
        To do so uncheck the "Use default manifest" and load a custom one, then chose a .tflite file containing model described in the manifest.</string>
    <string name="select">Here You can select a model to use (from the ones we provided or those that You have loaded yourself).
    Model You select is gone be run whenever You take a photo with the camera or pick one from gallery.</string>
</resources>